[
  {
    "question": "What mood or feeling might the poem evoke?",
    "choice1": "Anger",
    "choice2": "Sadness",
    "choice3": "Excitement",
    "choice4": "Peacefulness",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What literary device might be used in the poem?",
    "choice1": "Onomatopoeia",
    "choice2": "Alliteration",
    "choice3": "Simile",
    "choice4": "Personification",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What can you infer about the speaker’s relationship with sleep?",
    "choice1": "They are neutral about it",
    "choice2": "They enjoy it",
    "choice3": "They fear it",
    "choice4": "There’s no way to know",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the central theme of the poem?",
    "choice1": "Tranquility and serenity of the night",
    "choice2": "Nature",
    "choice3": "The imagery of tired roses, fragrant mignotte, and swaying lilies",
    "choice4": "Love",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the author use imagery to evoke a sense of place or emotion in the poem?",
    "choice1": "Dialogue between characters",
    "choice2": "Abstract and complex language",
    "choice3": "Vivid description of nature",
    "choice4": "Flashback and memories",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the author use sound devices like rhyme and rhythm in the poem?",
    "choice1": "Minimally",
    "choice2": "Occasionally",
    "choice3": "Extensively",
    "choice4": "Not at all",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of repetition in the poem, if any?",
    "choice1": "Adds complexity to the language",
    "choice2": "Reinforces a theme or emotion",
    "choice3": "Serves as a distraction",
    "choice4": "Has no discernible purpose",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the poem conclude?",
    "choice1": "With a surprising twist",
    "choice2": "With a resolution to a conflict",
    "choice3": "With an open-ended question",
    "choice4": "With a reflection on the theme",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the poet’s attitude towards the subject matter?",
    "choice1": "Indifferent",
    "choice2": "Enthusiastic",
    "choice3": "Critical",
    "choice4": "Ambiguous",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the author's purpose in writing the poem?",
    "choice1": "To entertain",
    "choice2": "To evoke emotions",
    "choice3": "To persuade",
    "choice4": "To inform",
    "answer": 2
  }
]
